Exit Art "Reactions" exhibit collection
Prints & Photographs Division, Library of Congress
- Silver, M.
  - [Untitled], 2044; 6; Submitted poem + jpg of painting via email--not sure if poet and painter are the same person
- Simko, Patricia
  - I "Heart" NY, photocopy of collage; 2045; 1536; I "heart shape" NY written in images of towers and heart-shaped bowl.
- Simko, Patricia
  - Ashes to Ashes (We All Fall Down), photocopy of collage; 2046; 1537; Three stacked images, top image of girl falling down, middle image of a tall building, bottom image of a firetruck
- Simko, Patricia
  - It Tolls for Thee, photocopy of collage; 2047; 1538; Three images, top two side by side: left image of doll with arm off, right image of girl crying, bottom image of firetruck
- Simko, Patricia
  - Goddess, photocopy of collage; 2048; 1539; Image of American flag with statue superimposed over it and animal's mouths with fangs about to devour the statue
- Simko, Patricia
  - Grief Has Taught Us Nothing, photocopy of collage; 2049; 1534; Collaged piece with image of crossed hands/gloves text in upper left corner "grief has taught us nothing"
- Simko, Patricia
  - The Twins, photocopy of collage; 2050; 1533; Collaged piece with image of two doos with hands clasped. Card in upper left corner reads: "The American Red Cross sends you good wishes of the folks at home"
- Simpson, Annie
  - [Untitled], 2051; 941; Love one
- Simpson, Patricia
  - The Flight to Freedom, 2053; 1821; Eagle
- Singer, Andy
  - [Untitled], 2054; 326; "Declaring..." 1 of 8
- Singer, Andy
  - [Untitled], 2055; 327; "Strategy for Afghanistan..." 2 of 8
- Singer, Andy
  - [Untitled], 2056; 328; "U.S. Humanitarian..." 3 of 8
- Singer, Andy
  - [Untitled], 2057; 329; "The Message We Convey..." 4 of 8
- Singer, Andy
  - [Untitled], 2058; 330; "Scary stories..." 5 of 8
- Singer, Andy
  - [Untitled], 2059; 331; "Why would anyone..." 6 of 8
- Singer, Andy
  - [Untitled], 2060; 332; "Modern News..." 7 of 8
- Singer, Andy
  - [Untitled], 2061; 333; "We should work..." 8 of 8
- Skye, Siofra Shaman
  - Coffee at the Comfort Diner, 2062; 251
- Sleeth, Wayne
  - [Untitled], 2064; 705; Non-fig. colofield
- Sloane, Janice
  - El Mundo, 2065; 2026; Blurry mask
- Sloat, Ben
  - The Attack, 2066; 1552; "Our spirits sinking..."
- Slutsky, Carolyn
  - [Untitled], 2068; 2270; I miss my towers...
- Smarch, Jr., Doug
  - [Untitled], photo; 2069; 922; Chair
- Smart Bks, Visual book Multiples
  - [Untitled], photo; 2069b; 1318
- Smith, Patricia
  - [Untitled], 2070; 636; Check
- Smith, Shinique Amie
  - Pabst Blue Ribbon: Coagulation No. 8, 2071; 3204; Red white blue painting
- Smith and Steve and Solveig Almaas, Ali
  - [Untitled], photo; 2072; 1379; Hand holding a candle and the word peace
- Smoler, Michael
  - The Talking Bird, copy of collage; 2073; 461
- Smoler, Michael
  - September 2001, copy of collage; 2074; 462
- Smoler, Michael
  - [Untitled], copy of collage; 2075; 463
- Smoler, Michael
  - The Things That Brings Us Together (a vision?), copy of collage; 2076; 464
- Smoler, Michael
  - I'm back you don't remember me the first time, copy of collage; 2077; 465
- Smoler, Michael
  - In Memory I, copy of collage; 2078; 466
- Smoler, Michael
  - In Memory II, copy of collage; 2079; 467; Cupid
- Smoler, Michael
  - In Memory III, copy of collage; 2080; 468; Plate, WTC background
- Soliman, Ania
  - [Untitled], digital image collage; 2081; 1073; 2 photos of Afghani fighters, with text
- Sollars, Chris
  - [Untitled], drawing; 2083; 1831; Towers in a glass of water
- Soller, Helaine
  - The Moment Our World Changed, print; 2084; 1021; Figures standing in the foreground
- Solmi, Federico
  - Man (part of "people" drawings installation), mixed media on paper; 2085; 1092; Red outline of a head in profile facing to the right I
- Somerville, David
  - Sad Angel: New York City, pen on paper; 2086; 1495; Drawing of a sad angel sitting in foreground w/red cross symbol on chest
- Son, Han s
  - [Untitled], 2087; 520; Stacked crates
- Sorgi, Jill
  - [Untitled], image transfer; 2088; 781; Flag image on paper
- Soros, Jeffrey
  - [Untitled], 2089; 2182
- Spek, Inez van der
  - [Untitled], 2090; 253; Email, "Dearest Lisa,"
- Spektor, Jenya
  - [Untitled], 2091; 203; "Exit" (interior of plane)
- Spitzer, Karin
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2092; 750; "no time for war" is repeated along vertical bands
- Spodarek, Diane Faith
  - Yesterday I Knew, photo and poem; 2093; 1502
- St. Cry, Brian
  - [Untitled], photograph; 2094; 2115; Folded hands
- St. Cyr, Richard
  - [Untitled], photograph; 2095; 2114; Small dark figure in field of grass
- St. Joesph's School for the Deaf
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 2096; 1741; 1741-1750; God bless America
- St. Joseph's School for the Deaf
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 2097; 1742; 1741-1750; good job heroes
- St. Joseph's School for the Deaf
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 2098; 1744; 1741-1750; peace on earth
- St. Joseph's School for the Deaf
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 2099a; 1746; 1741-1750; christmas tree and WTC
- St. Joseph School for the Deaf
  - God bless America and peace, pencil on paper; 2099b; 1743; 1741-1750
- St. Joseph's School for the Deaf
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 2099c; 1747; 1741-1750; flag and eagle
- St. Joseph's School for the Deaf
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 2100; 1748; 1741-1750; may the earth be peaceful
- St. Joseph's School for the Deaf
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 2100b; 1745; 1741-1750; peace sign
- St. Joseph's School for the Deaf
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 2101; 1750; 1741-1750; God bless WTC
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 2101c; 1749; 1741-1750; I love America
- Staib, Barbara
  - Reaction, 2102; 1761; Abstract image with lines, bubbles and patches of shading
- Staib, Barbara
  - reaction, 2103; 1762; Abstract image with what looks like clouds and the tail of an airplane
- Staib, Barbara
  - reaction, 2105; 1761; Abstract image with lines, bubbles and patches of shading
- Stambaugh, Stacey
  - Sorry, sorry ..., drawing (letter picture); 2106; 1247
- Stamos, William George
  - [Untitled], 2107; 1789
- Stanford, Ruth A.
  - [Untitled], turkey target, text from radio news broadcasts, 9-11-9-13; 2108; 395; Green and black
- Starmack
  - [Untitled], crayon drawing; 2109; 967; WTC
- Stedman, Emily
  - [Untitled], 2110; 348; Greenwich Street 9/11 Code Blue 2001 drawing
- Stein, Erik
  - They Changed the Flag, 2111; 536
- Stein, Jonathan
  - [Untitled], 2112; 641; Outline bird
- Steiner, Clara
  - [Untitled], collage; 2114; 319
- Steinhauer, Eddie
  - The New Normal, 2115; 1698
- Steinweiss, Alex
  - Stop Hate, digital print; 2116; 515
- Stephan
  - [Untitled], paint on paper; 2116b; 3248
- Stephens, Elizabeth
  - [Untitled], 2117; 2131; I hate terrorism, I hate the war against terrorism
- Stephens, K.
  - [Untitled], 2118; 2275; I have already alternately...
- Stephens, Richard
  - Diary of Abib, text on paper; 2120; 841; Poem
- Stephens, Richard
  - [Untitled], oil paint on cardboard; 2121; 840; Two long verticle rectangles in center of page
- Susi, Steve
  - [Untitled], 2122; 615; Text in images of towers Americans side by side
- Stevens, May
  - [Untitled], 2124; 1332; Lonely appear
- Stevens, Rachel
  - Small City, photograph of steel and netting; 2125; 1030; Image of two skyscrapers made of white translucent netting with people standing inside them
- Stevens, Stef
  - Stones at Beach, 2126; 1970; NYC skyline on beach
- Stewart, Christine
  - [Untitled], 2127; 1329; Fruits
- Stitt, Andre
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2128; 872; Black wings
- Stone, Laurie
  - Another Kind of Bioterrorism, 2129; 2143; "A week or so after..."
- Stone, Laurie
  - After the Bodies Fell, 2130; 3061
- Stone, Mildred
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 2131; 1567; Figure drawing of man with handwritten text down center
- Stone, Todd
  - [Untitled], photograph; 2132; 937; I am a D-boy
- Strada da Ravenna, Giovanni
  - [Untitled], 2133; 63; 1 of 2 artwork via email
- Strada de Ravenna, Giovanni
  - [Untitled], 2133b; 64; Half-circle w/Italian magazine photo of manhattan w/smoke
- Strande, Sue
  - Fission, 2135; 1852; Naked girls and women
- Strano, Fernando
  - [Untitled], drawing and column of text; 2136; 1978
- Strasbourg-Thompson, Barry
  - Sept. 11, 2001, digital print of acrylic painting on canvas; 2137; 261; Print of painting acrylic on canvas
- Strecker, Megan
  - [Untitled], 2138; 415; Organic shapes
- Strow, Diza
  - [Untitled], 2139; 1169; Toy cars
- Stylianou, Theopisti
  - [Untitled], photo; 2140; 600; Photo of protest
- Sugitatsu, Yoshi
  - [Untitled], photo; 2141; 221
- Sigurdardottir, Thorgerdur
  - [Untitled], 2142; 562; Cross in square
- Sullivan, Susan
  - September 11, 2001, 2144; 668
- Surach, Nicole
  - [Untitled], 2145; 210; Part of group from students of the Hudson School, "A nation..."
- Svethrilova, Chanika
  - [Untitled], 2146; 1239; "the US is a land which is..."
- Swales, Peter J.
  - [Untitled], 2148; 926; MacDonalds
- Swangstu, Eric
  - Response Drawing, smoke on paper; 2149; 1597; Smoke and heart
- Swangstu, Janel
  - American Sign Language - I Love You, silk screen ink and carbon on paper; 2150; 1596
- Sweeney, Jenna
  - [Untitled], 2151; 1964; "Its been 13 hours..."
- Sykes, Jill
  - Fractured Premonitions, copy of oil on canvas painting; 2152; 846
- Sykes, Sandy
  - Black Moon, japanese woodcut, water-based print of sumi ink on handmade washi paper; 2153; 1075; Image of a large black circle printed slightly offset on white paper. www.sandysykes.co.uk
- Sylvester, Marc
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 2154; 1024; Text "911" written
- Sympson, Melanie
  - Chicago 11/01, 2155; 1216; Moon
- Szalla, Jason D.
  - The New Language, 5/5; 2156; 452
- Szalla, Jason D.
  - Photograph Not Available, a/p; 2157; 451
- Szefer Karlsen, Anne
  - [Untitled], photograph; 2158; 1366
- Szyszka, Roswita
  - Voices Within, 2159; 377; Emailed image
- Tabios, Eileen
  - [Untitled], 2160; 113; Poem
- Tacha, Athena
  - [Untitled], 2161; 359; "To the new york times editor..."
- Talaie, Ramin
  - [Untitled], photograph; 2162; 1776; Girls w/candle
- Tamaaki, Ikeguchi
  - [Untitled], color print; 2162b; 3273
- Tamaaki, Ikeguchi
  - [Untitled], color print; 2162c; 3274
- Tamisiea, Jeanne
  - [Untitled], 2163; 2185; The planes 1 of 7
- Tamisiea, Jeanne
  - [Untitled], 2164; 2186; Courage not fear 2 of 7
- Tamisiea, Jeanne
  - [Untitled], 2165; 2187; What happens 3 of 7
- Tamisiea, Jeanne
  - [Untitled], 2166; 2188; No one will stop us 4 of 7
- Tamisiea, Jeanne
  - [Untitled], 2167; 2189; Calendar 5 of 7
- Tamisiea, Jeanne
  - [Untitled], 2168; 2190; Statue of liberty 6 of 7
- Tamisiea, Jeanne
  - [Untitled], 2169; 2191; Statue of liberty 7 of 7
- Tandy, Nadina
  - [Untitled], 2171; 392
- Tarantino, Allan
  - As Long As We Still Have Beer in Brooklyn, color photo with black marker; 2172; 775
- Tarkett-Reed, Lisa
  - [Untitled], journal entries; 2173; 365
- Tatara, Jill
  - Walking Home from Chambers and Church, text on paper; 2174; 1448; Poem
- Tatara, Jill
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2175; 1447; 2 dark ovals within two vertical rectangles
- Tatem, Sue Binkley
  - [Untitled], color xerox; 2175b; 3254
- Tattelman, Ira
  - Scratch, 2176; 887; Photo of windows
- Tavernise, Linda
  - Retablo for Those Who Jumped, 2177; 1476; Image of man falling from WTC with a small plane in upper righthand corner
- Taylor, Elyse
  - Memorial, 2178; 428; Color print
- Taylor, Leah
  - [Untitled], color copy; 2178b; 3269
- Taylor, Morgan
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 2179; 2107; Perspective drawing of city block
- Taylor, Sali
  - Around Zero Life Lines, 2180; 527
- Taylor, Shan
  - [Untitled], text on color photograph; 2181; 773; Color photo of a male's bruised face w/stitches in upper lip. Poem is printed on the photo upside down
- Teele, Kate
  - [Untitled], 2182; 663; Circular
- Temkina, Marina
  - [Untitled], text with photo; 2183; 456; "Psalm by King..."
- Cate ten, Ritsaert
  - [Untitled], 2184; 13; JPG via email
- Terry, Nick
  - The First Thing I Saw, sandpaper; 2185; 915
- Teteriantnikov, Savva
  - [Untitled], 2186; 632; Ants on flag
- The Friendliest Black Artist in America
  - [Untitled], text; 2187; 1589
- Thieriot, India
  - [Untitled], 2188; 68; Artwork via mail
- Think Again
  - Act Like It's a Globe, inkjet print; 2189; 654; 1 of 2
- Think Again
  - Terrorist Organization, inkjet print; 2190; 653; 2 of 2
- Thomas
  - [Untitled], 2191; 1648; Image of pig in overalls building a brickhouse with text behind it. "A pound of flesh" is written across the top right of page
- Borland, Brett
  - REACTION, 2192; 387; "Two years ago..."
- Thomas, Bryan Valentine
  - [Untitled], graphite and gesso on paper; 2193; 994; Two parallel and horizontal black bars running through center of page, perpendicular to a black bar running down left side of page.
- Thomas, Gwenn
  - [Untitled], 2194; 1232; Fingerprints
- Thomas, Judy
  - [Untitled], 2195; 2005; I called in late for work that day
- Thomas, Richard
  - [Untitled], photograph; 2196; 338; Prayer Tree, Thailand, Sept. 2001
- Thomasine & Samantha
  - [Untitled], 2197; 548; 11 of 16
- Thompson, Calla
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 2198; 982; Line drawing of men with connected gas masks standing to the left of a microphone
- Thorjussen, Tanja
  - [Untitled], 2199; 1884; Statue of liberty w/twin towers in sky
- Thurmer. Robert
  - [Untitled], 2200; 597; Critique of art post 9/11
- Tice, Michael
  - [Untitled], watercolor drawing; 2201; 364; "Time: Angel or Devil?"
- Kastor, Tiki
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 2202; 1471
- Tisa, Charles
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2203; 786; Small line drawings
- Tiscornia, Ana
  - Re-Action, digital images on paper; 2204; 995; 9 images arranged in a geometrical square pattern, each with a title underneath
- Tisdale, Elizabeth
  - [Untitled], 2205; 1091; Image of a woman praying in the foreground against a background image of the burning trade center
- Toliver, Tomiko
  - [Untitled], 2206; 1557
- Tompkins, Betty
  - [Untitled], 2207; 314; Teddy bears
- Toole, Christa
  - [Untitled], 2208; 901; Colored chalk organic looking
- Toporowicz, Maciej
  - [Untitled], jet ink print; 2209; 283; WTC #1
- Topper, Renee
  - Accepting Angels, text on paper; 2210; 778; Poem
- Torre, S.
  - WTC 010911 9:15 AM, poem; 2211; 2173
- Torres, Edwin
  - I Saw You Empire State Building, 2213; 1876; Poem
- Torres, Samuel
  - We Appreciate Your Business, 2214; 1518
- Torres Vega, Sally
  - [Untitled], 2215; 1136; Cardboard and key
- Tragant, Guillermo
  - Twin Towers, 2216; 1971; Push/pull
- Trager, Amanda
  - [Untitled], 2217; 2037; "This image is certainly a work of art"
- Trattner, Marsha
  - [Untitled], 2218; 1227; Image from Pipe Dreams
- Triana, Gladys
  - I am here: working, 2219; 952; Photos of her hands
- Trigg, Sarah
  - McFabric, 2220; 1643; Elliptical pattern covering entire page
- Troeger, Andreas
  - [Untitled], 2221; 1215
- Tsai, Eric
  - [Untitled], paper; 2222; 1473; Cut and woven white sheet of paper
- Tsam
  - Reactions 9/11, photography; 2223; 1621; Guy on cell phone
- Tucker, Angela
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 2224; 1564; Jumbled collage of images and handwritten words
- Tucker, Daniel
  - [Untitled], 2225; 1546; "Dude, that taliban shit..."
- Tucker, Peter
  - [Untitled], 2226; 1052; Installing instructions
- Turley, Shelley
  - [Untitled], 2227; 1475; Drawing of nurse standing over patient w/a swan in the background
- Turner, Kellis
  - Enemy Mine, pencil on paper; 2229; 764; Hand written poem on paper
- Turner, Kellis
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 2230; 1097; Images of George Bush and Osama Bin Laden dueling with the twin towers
- Tweed, Heather
  - Untitled (NY 2001), 2232; 114; WWW.heathertweed.co.uk
- Twomey, Chris
  - [Untitled], 2233; 417
- Tyc, Catherine
  - [Untitled], 2234; 109; 3 pages of poem text
- Tyler, Christine
  - [Untitled], 2235; 3285
- Uehling, Judith
  - [Untitled], 2236; 970; Digital w/flag
- Uhde, Dagmar
  - [Untitled], 2237; 1787; Words in German and English
- Ullman, Debbie
  - [Untitled], 2238; 1848; American flag question mark
- Ulrich, Antoinette
  - Primary Colors- with Light Domination, photo of painting; 2239; 698
- Ulrike Soika, Karin
  - [Untitled], 2240; 661; "Freedom..."
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color print; 2241b; 3305; Heal with peace sign
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color print; 2241c; 3306; Hand print red white and blue
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color print; 2241d; 3307; Pink shadow of woman and planes
- unknown
  - [Untitled], via email; 2241e; 3308; Black and white lines
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color printout; 2241f; 3309; Photo factory with laser geometric shape
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color printout; 2241g; 3310; Photo of square with laser geometric printout
- unknown
  - [Untitled], copy of photo; 2241h; 3311; Minature chair on rock
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color photo; 2241i; 3312; Street at night with smoke in back ground
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color photo; 2241j; 3313; Missing people signs on Guess ad.
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color photo; 2241k; 3314; Washsq: flag with boys
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color photo; 2241l; 3315; Washsq: flag with girl
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color photo; 2241m; 3316; Candles
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color photo; 2241n; 3317; People with empire state building
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color photo; 2241o; 3318; I Love You Dad
- unknown
  - [Untitled], color photo; 2241p; 3319; Peace sign light with american flag
- unknown
  - [Untitled], text; 2241q; 3320; Cinamatic reflections on the recent apocalyptic events
- Unknown
  - [Untitled], color photo; 2241r; 3321; Bronze sculpture of woman sitting
- Valado, Rosa
  - [Untitled], photograph; 2242; 2103; Photo of a hexagon shaped sculpture made of wire
- Valentin, Ben
  - [Untitled], text; 2242b; 3278; CRASH!
- Valentine, Christina
  - [Untitled], 2243; 2128
- Vinh, La Toan
  - Re-action, drawing; 2244; 566; Muslims praying 1 of 4
- Valero, Aurora
  - Are you hopeful?, painting; 2246; 860
- Valla, Teresa
  - [Untitled], 2247; 290; Picture of war protestors by candlelight
- Valla, Teresa
  - [Untitled], 2248; 291; Hate free zone w/man
- Valla, Teresa
  - [Untitled], 2249; 292; Candlelight
- Van der Ploeg, Jan
  - [Untitled], 2250; 762; Image of 4 elongated ovals and 1 small circle
- Van Diggele, Adeyanne H.
  - An Attack in the Heart, photo with writing around; 2251; 280
- van Doxell, Nathalie
  - Endurance of Love, Hearts, Antinationalism, 2252; 266; Belly
- Van Eldik, Theo
  - sorrow, poem; 2252b; 3233
- Van Helden, Sylvie
  - December 11, 2001, 2253; 2167
- Vander Meer, Kerry
  - Tight as a Knot, 2255; 924
- Varone, Jason
  - [Untitled], color print; 2255b; 3221
- Vegas, Jill
  - Who wants to be a widow?, photo and text; 2256; 509
- Velazquez, Yolanda
  - [Untitled], 2257; 231; "...miedo"
- Verdoux, Jeanne
  - [Untitled], 2258; 2200; 1-- NY 1 of 2
- Verdoux, Jeanne
  - [Untitled], 2259; 2201; Missing 2 of 2
- Verselli, Laura J.
  - [Untitled], 2260; 146; "September 11, 2001," from Mt Ida College drawing class.
- Victor, Carmen J.
  - 3rd Floor, archival digital print; 2261; 1430; Photo of a woman standing in the corner of a low ceilinged room
- Viera, Conny
  - [Untitled], 2262; 677; Word searches 1 of 2
- Viera, Conny
  - [Untitled], 2263; 676; Word searches 2 of 2
- Viera, Diane
  - Good Vibrations, 2264; 2024
- Villasenor, Maria-Christina
  - [Untitled], 2265; 3217; Violence breeds violence boy
- Villasmil, Alejandra
  - Impressions, oil and masking tape on cardboard; 2266; 928; Thumbprints
- Vine, Rachel
  - [Untitled], photos; 2267; 246; Series of photos of WTC collapsing
- Vines, Jr., Richard
  - [Untitled], 2268; 719; Quote from Christopher Dawson, "As soon as men decide that all means are permitted to fight evil, then their good becomes indistinguishable from the evil that they set out to destroy"
- Vinh, La Toan
  - [Untitled], 2269; 565; Eye NYC 2 of 4
- Vinh, La Toan
  - [Untitled], 2270; 564; Heart 3 of 4
- Vinh, La Toan
  - [Untitled], 2271; 563; Painted face
- Vinh, La Toan
  - Mail, ink on paper; 2272; 1258; Mail by Ray Johnson, drawing of a cartoon face and text
- Vinh, La Toan
  - Mail, mixed media; 2273; 1259; Text collage of the names of cities w/"New York" circled
- Vinogradova, Vica
  - [Untitled], 2274; 3017; Via email
- Vitolins, Andris
  - [Untitled], 2277; 1346; 3 figs at table.
- Vizzini, Ned
  - [Untitled], 2278; 363; "12/5/01..."
- Von Prittwitz, Tatjana
  - The Attacks from a European Perspective, text on paper; 2279; 831; An article which she authored published in thebardfreepress.vol3.issue2 Tatjana Von Prottwitz works at the Center for Curatorial Studies
- von Roon, Yasmin
  - [Untitled], marker on paper; 2280; 110; Artwork via mail sent by mother, Yasmin Albert, of child's drawing of towers and planes w/sun in the middle
- von Rydingvard, Ursula
  - As To The Memorial, 2281; 1418; Essay on white paper
- von Zweck, Dina
  - 9/11/01 The Furies Unleash Themselves, 2282; 530; 1 of 3
- von Zweck, Dina
  - WTC, 2283; 529; 2 of 3
- Zweck, Dina von
  - Glass House--Synopsis, 2284; 528; 3 of 3
- VonRydirgsvard-Green, Ursula
  - My Sculpture, photographs; 2285; 1265; Photos of a young child building with blocks and wearing a ventilation mask
- Voorhees, Chris
  - [Untitled], text on paper; 2286; 805; A typed letter from Chris to Carolyn
- Wachs, Joel
  - [Untitled], 2287; 308; "The Show Must Go On"
- Walch, Meg
  - Shocking Crashes and Chases, 2288; 2126; I will never forget that night...
- Walls, Sherry
  - [Untitled], 2290; 2138; "Where I live most people drive to work"
- Waldeck, Robert
  - Whatever You Do They Are On To You, digital print; 2293; 801; Two images side by side with printed text
- Wallace, Robert
  - Never Forever, paper collage; 2294; 1103; Abstract paper design
- Wands, Cynthia
  - [Untitled], color print; 2295; 3230
- Ward, Cathy
  - Unraveling DNA, color copy; 2295b; 3244
- Ward, Marshall
  - [Untitled], 2296; 585; Flag and tallies
- Warshaw, Larry
  - [Untitled], 2297; 312; "Missing..."
- Warshaw, Larry
  - [Untitled], 2298; 313; "Four thousand missing..."
- Washburn, Electra
  - [Untitled], 2299; 1234; Marker flag
- Wasilik, Jeanne Marie
  - [Untitled], 2300; 1211; Drawing w/Wordsworth poem
- Wasko, Richard
  - Breaking News, 2301; 2171
- Wasserman, Claire
  - Reflections, 2302; 1509; Hands and wire
- Watkinson & Phillis Anne DuCoyne, James F.
  - Disappearance & Dissaray, photographs; 2303; 1365; Photograph on NYC skyline on above photograph of a woman in a dissarayed office on bottom
- Watson, Jennifer
  - [Untitled], 2304; 976; Mannequin
- Watson, Laura
  - Afghani Women, oil on canvas; 2305; 1953; Woman and child
- Waxman, Wendy
  - What Do I Stand For?, 2306; 2273; Rather than looking at what we...
- Webb, Brett
  - [Untitled], artwork; 2308; 79; Artwork via email
- Webb, Kurt Brian
  - Death Days, woodcut; 2309; 2081; Skeleton, plane, ship
- Weber, Bruce
  - [Untitled], 2310; 2278
- Weber, Marshall
  - [Untitled], 2311; 35; Whatever cache you people...
- Webster, Susannah
  - Let Them Eat Cake, digital video stills; 2312; 929; 1 of 2
- Webster, Susannah
  - [Untitled], drawing; 2313; 930; Doublemint gum towers
- Wechsler, Arnold
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2315; 1421; Abstract cubist image with dark background
- Wechsler, Arnold
  - [Untitled], digital image; 2316; 1515
- Wegman, William
  - [Untitled], essay with drawings on paper; 2317; 759
- Weina Zhao, Ines Zimmerman, Judith Uathrein
  - Waiting for Peace, mixed media collage; 2318; 1002; Solid black background with collaged dove on left side of page. Collaboration of Judith Uathrein, Weina Zhao, Ines Zimmerman
- Uathrein, Judith; Zhao, Weina; Zimmerman, Ines
  - Victim Nr. 460132, crayon on paper; 2319; 1003; Collaboration of Judith Uathrein, Weina Zhao and Ines Zimmerman, background of black crayon with a simplistic human form near center of page and the words "Victim Nr. 460132" in lower righthand corner
- Weinberg, Louise